<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Oka bRionZ Blog</title>
    <link>https://www.okabrionz.com/blog/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Oka bRionZ Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>id-id</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 14 Jul 2017 01:44:01 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://www.okabrionz.com/blog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Five Secrets for Successful Negotiation</title>
      <link>https://www.okabrionz.com/blog/post/five-secrets-for-successful-negotiation/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Jul 2017 01:44:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.okabrionz.com/blog/post/five-secrets-for-successful-negotiation/</guid>
      <description>An adept negotiator uses skillful techniques to reach a deal without aggression. While negotiation skills can require some practice, becoming a good negotiator is within reach. It just requires following some basic guidelines that focus on the ultimate goal: successfully reaching an agreement acceptable to both parties.
Here are five tips for negotiating successfully.
1. Prepare yourself with facts Before entering into a negotiation, arm yourself with factual information. Get as much information as you can that is relevant to the subject of negotiations.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Nama Domain Itu Apaan Sih?</title>
      <link>https://www.okabrionz.com/blog/post/nama-domain-itu-apaan-sih/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Jul 2017 11:58:15 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.okabrionz.com/blog/post/nama-domain-itu-apaan-sih/</guid>
      <description>Kenapa pake nama domain segala ya?, kan repot harus bayar per/ tahunnya. Iya juga sih kalo mau punya nama domain kita harus bayar pertahun dengan biaya sesuai eksistensi yang kita suka. Misalnya okabrionz.com, Saya sewa nama domain ini sekitar Rp. 150.000,- / per tahunnya.
Si Kepo: Kenapa atuh ente rela bayar tiap tahun buat nama domain?
Ane: Karena kalo ga pake nama domain bisa ribet agan ngunjungin lagi website ane, kan kalo sekarang mau baca lagi artikel lain yang ane bikin tinggal ketik aja okabrionz.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Professional Managed Virtual Machine Service Domain Name</title>
      <link>https://www.okabrionz.com/blog/post/vpssg-com-is-for-sale/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Mar 2017 14:36:46 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.okabrionz.com/blog/post/vpssg-com-is-for-sale/</guid>
      <description>A Cloud domain is really crowded and it was impossible to register good domain name, so I jump to anything similar with cloud, virtual server, or hosting words. And, I got it now. ManagedVM.com is really awesome domain name on hosting niche.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ManagedVM.com</title>
      <link>https://www.okabrionz.com/blog/post/managedvm-com/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Mar 2017 19:44:07 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.okabrionz.com/blog/post/managedvm-com/</guid>
      <description>ManagedVM.com is High Opportunity domain name for web hosting company, no better than this name. Let&amp;rsquo;s talk it word by word, Managed mean is a service who has managed by professional and then the VM mean is Virtual Machine.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A beginners’ guide to brewing with Chemex</title>
      <link>https://www.okabrionz.com/blog/post/brewing-chemex/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Jan 2017 15:04:10 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.okabrionz.com/blog/post/brewing-chemex/</guid>
      <description>This week we’ll take a look at all the steps required to make astonishing coffee with a Chemex at home. The Chemex Coffeemaker is a manual, pour-over style glass-container coffeemaker that Peter Schlumbohm invented in 1941, and which continues to be manufactured by the Chemex Corporation in Chicopee, Massachusetts*.
In 1958, designers at the Illinois Institute of Technology said that the Chemex Coffeemaker is &amp;ldquo;one of the best-designed products of modern times&amp;rdquo;, and so is included in the collection of the Museum of Modern Art in New York City.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Just in: small batch of Jamaica Blue Mountain in store next week</title>
      <link>https://www.okabrionz.com/blog/post/jamaica-blue/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Jan 2017 15:04:10 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.okabrionz.com/blog/post/jamaica-blue/</guid>
      <description>We expect the shipment of a limited quantity of green beans next Monday. We’ll be offering the roasted beans from Tuesday, but quantities are limited, so be quick.
Blue Mountain Peak is the highest mountain in Jamaica and one of the highest peaks in the Caribbean at 7,402 ft. It is the home of Blue Mountain coffee and their famous tours. It is located on the border of the Portland and Saint Thomas parishes of Jamaica.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Making sense of the SCAA’s new Flavor Wheel</title>
      <link>https://www.okabrionz.com/blog/post/making-sense/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Dec 2016 15:04:10 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.okabrionz.com/blog/post/making-sense/</guid>
      <description>The SCAA updated the wheel to reflect the finer nuances needed to describe flavors more precisely. The new descriptions are more detailed and hence allow cuppers to distinguish between more flavors.
While this is going to be a big change for professional coffee tasters, it means a lot to you as a consumer as well. We’ll explain how the wheel came to be, how pros use it and what the flavors actually mean.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About Oka bRionZ</title>
      <link>https://www.okabrionz.com/blog/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.okabrionz.com/blog/about/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact</title>
      <link>https://www.okabrionz.com/blog/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.okabrionz.com/blog/contact/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Our Coffee</title>
      <link>https://www.okabrionz.com/blog/products/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.okabrionz.com/blog/products/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Privacy - Oka bRionZ</title>
      <link>https://www.okabrionz.com/blog/privacy/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.okabrionz.com/blog/privacy/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Values</title>
      <link>https://www.okabrionz.com/blog/values/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.okabrionz.com/blog/values/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>